Guide to the World Student Christian Federation North America Regional Office Records
Yale University Divinity School Library
- Inter-regional Office and Regional Offices of the World Student Christian Federation, Series III
  - Regional Offices
    - Africa
      - Correspondence, 1978-1979 (Box 22, Folder 406)
      - ARC meeting - Nairobi, Kenya, 1979 May 26-Jun 1 (Box 22, Folder 407)
      - Correspondence, 1981-1984, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 408)
      - Correspondence re. Africa conferences, 1985-1986 (Box 22, Folder 409)
      - Africa Regional Workshop report - Kenya, 1985 Oct 28-Nov 1 (Box 22, Folder 410)
      - National Movements and Contacts, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 411)
      - Global Survival Consultation - Kenya, 1986 Jul 17-20 (Box 22, Folder 412-414)
      - Leadership Workshop Women Consultation - Liberia, 1986 Sep 8-16 (Box 22, Folder 415)
      - Christian Student Council - Kenya, 1986-1987 (Box 22, Folder 416)
    - Asia/Pacific
      - Materials re. Solidarity with Korea, 1973, 1979-1980 (Box 22, Folder 417)
      - Praxis - WSCF Asia Newsletter, 1976, 1978-1979 (Box 22, Folder 418)
      - Report on Activities, 1977-1978 (Box 22, Folder 419)
      - Material re. China, 1978, n.d. (Box 23, Folder 420)
      - Reports, 1981-1982 (Box 23, Folder 421)
      - Correspondence, 1981-1983 (Box 23, Folder 422)
      - A Brief Summary of Major Programme Events, 1981-1985 (Box 23, Folder 423)
      - WSCF-CCA Consultation on Ecumenical Task of Asian SCM, 1982 (Box 23, Folder 424)
      - Human Resources Development Programme Report, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 425)
      - CCA-WSCF Joint Consultation on "Critical Review of the Vision and Reality of University in Society", 1985 (Box 23, Folder 426)
      - Material re. Korean protest of President Chun's visit to U.S., 1985 Apr (Box 23, Folder 427)
      - Regional Committee meeting - Mexico City (minutes), 1986 Mar 3-7 (Box 23, Folder 428)
      - Correspondence/Action Alerts, 1987 (Box 23, Folder 429)
    - Europe
      - Newsletter, 1972, 1978-1980, 1982 (Box 23, Folder 430)
      - European Students' Conference - Lillehammer, Norway, 1975 Sep 25-30 (Box 23, Folder 431)
      - Committee minutes (miscellaneous), 1976-1978 (Box 23, Folder 432)
      - Campaign Against the Model West Germany, 1977 (Box 23, Folder 433)
      - Correspondence, 1977-1980 (Box 23, Folder 434)
      - Programme, 1978 (Box 23, Folder 435)
      - European Students' Conference - Athens, 1978 Apr 18-23 (Box 23, Folder 436)
      - Women's Project Commission, 1978 (Box 23, Folder 437)
      - Women's Project Newsletter, 1979-1980 (Box 23, Folder 438)
      - Committee minutes (miscellaneous), 1979-1980 (Box 23, Folder 439)
      - Correspondence, 1981-1982 (Box 24, Folder 440)
      - Women's Working Group minutes, 1981, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 441)
      - Working Group Reports, 1981-1986 (Box 24, Folder 442)
      - Up-Date (WSCF Europe newsletter), 1983-1986 (Box 24, Folder 443)
      - Correspondence, 1983, 1985-1986 (Box 24, Folder 444-445)
      - European Regional Assembly - Valamo, Finland: Correspondence, preparatory material (Box 24, Folder 446)
      - European Regional Assembly - Valamo, Finland: Minutes, report, 1985 Aug 12-13 (Box 24, Folder 447)
      - European Regional Committee: London (minutes), 1986 Feb 5-9 (Box 24, Folder 448)
      - European Regional Committee: Berlin, GDR (minutes), 1987 Apr 21-26 (Box 24, Folder 449)
      - European Regional Committee: Boldern, Switzerland (minutes), 1987 Aug 16-19 (Box 24, Folder 450)
      - European Regional Committee: Bodenfelde, FRG, 1988 Dec 4-9 (Box 24, Folder 451)
      - European Regional Committee: Women's Working Group - Bodenfelde, FRG, 1987 Dec 10-13 (Box 24, Folder 452)
      - Darmstadt European Co-Ordination, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 453)
    - Latin America
      - Federacion Universal de Movimientos Estudiantiles Cristianos en America Latina Y El Caribe: Requests for ESF Grants, 1980 (Box 24, Folder 454)
      - Correspondence, 1981-1982 (Box 24, Folder 455)
      - FUMEC Newsletter, flyers, 1982, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 456)
      - Serie: Documentos, 1982-1983 (Box 24, Folder 457)
      - Correspondence, 1984-1985, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 458)
      - Regional Women's Commission, 1984 Oct 4-7 (Box 24, Folder 459)
      - VI Asamblea Continental - Managua, Nicaragua, 1985 Jun 9-16 (Box 24, Folder 460)
    - Middle East
      - Student Leaders Conference Leadership Development Programme, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 461)
- Related Ecumenical Student Movements, Series IV
  The movements in this Series are grouped into two general categories: 1)North American movements, which include statewide and regional movements and local movements; and 2)Non-North American movements, including national movements and local movements.
  - North American Movements
    - Statewide and Regional Movements
      - Correspondence, 1972, 1976-1978 (Box 25, Folder 462)
      - Meeting minutes, 1975-1977 (Box 25, Folder 463)
      - Budget, funding proposals, 1973-1981 (Box 25, Folder 464)
      - Conferences, programs, workshops, 1974-1978, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 465-468)
      - Newsletters, brochures, 1976-1977, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 469)
      - John Boonstra's notes and collected articles, 1976-1977, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 470)
      - Miscellaneous documents, 1969, 1973, 1976 (Box 25, Folder 471)
      - Cuba Project, 1977 (Box 25, Folder 472)
      - Miscellaneous documents, 1981-1983 (Box 25, Folder 473-475)
      - 50th Anniversary Celebration, 1984 Oct 20 (Box 25, Folder 476)
      - Correspondence, 1985 (Box 25, Folder 477)
      - Campus Ministry Conference - Newton Centre, MA, 1985 Mar 4 (Box 25, Folder 478)
      - Newsletters, brochures, 1985-1986, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 479)
      - Exposure Tour of the Philippines - Report, 1986 (Box 25, Folder 480)
      - Fall Conference - University of New Hampshire, 1986 (Box 26, Folder 481)
      - Board of Directors meeting - Boston, 1986 Sep 19-21 (Box 26, Folder 482)
      - Correspondence, 1986-1987 (Box 26, Folder 483)
      - Spring Conference - "Thinking Globally, Acting Locally", 1987 (Box 26, Folder 484-485)
      - Fall Conference - University of Massachusetts, Amherst, 1987 Nov 6-8 (Box 26, Folder 486)
      - Correspondence, 1988 (Box 26, Folder 487)
      - Student Conference - "What is the University Preparing You For?" - Brown University, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 488)
      - Student Christian Movement in Pennsylvania, 1984 (Box 26, Folder 489)
    - Local Movements
      - Mount St. Vincent University Student Christian Movement: Project "Christianity and Homosexuality", Halifax, Nova Scotia, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 490-491)
      - University of Toronto, 1986 Nov (Box 26, Folder 492)
      - York Student Christian Movement - York University, Ontario, 1979, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 493)
  - Non-North American Movements
    - National Movements
      - Australia--Australian Student Christian Movement: Correspondence, 1979-1980, 1985 (Box 26, Folder 494)
      - Australia--Australian Student Christian Movement: National Newsletter, 1978-1980 (Box 26, Folder 495)
      - Australia--Australian Student Christian Movement: "Across the Currents", National Newsletter, 1981-1983 (Box 26, Folder 496)
      - Australia--Australian Student Christian Movement: Collected publications re. Australia, 1978, 1986 (Box 26, Folder 497)
      - Cuba - Student Christian Movement of Cuba, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 498)
      - Dominican Republic - Movimiento Estudiantil Cristiano Republica Dominicana, 1987-1988 (Box 26, Folder 499)
      - El Salvador - Movimiento Estudiantil Cristiano de El Salvador, 1984 (Box 26, Folder 500)
      - Hong Kong - Student Christian Movement of Hong Kong, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 501)
      - India - Student Christian Movement of India, 1979-1981 (Box 26, Folder 502)
      - Italy - Federazione Giovanile Evangelica Italiana, 1984-1988 (Box 27, Folder 503)
      - Liberia - National Student Christian Council of Liberia, 1986-1987 (Box 27, Folder 504)
      - New Zealand - New Zealand Student Christian Movement, 1986 (Box 27, Folder 505)
      - Norway - Student Christian Movement of Norway, 1978, 1981, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 506)
      - Philippines - Student Christian Movement of the Philippines: Arrests/Political Detainees, 1979-1980, 1985 (Box 27, Folder 507-508)
      - Philippines - Student Christian Movement of the Philippines: Materials re. Solidarity, 1985 (Box 27, Folder 509)
      - Philippines - Student Christian Movement of the Philippines: Publicity letter with historical information, 1986 Mar (Box 27, Folder 510)
      - Singapore - Students' Christian Movement of Singapore, 1977 Nov, 1983 Apr (Box 27, Folder 511)
      - Sri Lanka - Student Christian Movement of Sri Lanka, 1984 (Box 27, Folder 512)
      - Thailand - Thailand Student Christian Movement, 1988 (Box 27, Folder 513)
    - Local Movements
      - University of El Salvador, 1982 Jun (Box 27, Folder 514)
- Related Organizations, 1972-1998; Series V
  The organizations in this series are listed alphabetically. Subheadings are provided for the following organizations:
  Frontier Internship in Mission
  Lutheran Student Movement in Canada
  Lutheran Student Movement in the U.S.A.
  United Methodist Church - Board of Global Ministries
  United Ministries in Education
  Young Christians for Global Justice
  - Agape (International Ecumenical Study Centre), 1984 (Box 28, Folder 515)
  - Alternate Province Working Committee, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 516)
  - Anti-Defamation League of B'nai B'rith, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 517)
  - Campus Ministry Women, 1977 Nov (Box 28, Folder 518)
  - Canadian Council of Churches - Canadian Ecumenical Youth Coalition, 1984, 1988 (Box 28, Folder 519)
  - Canadian Council of Churches - Commission on the Church and the University, 1958 (Box 28, Folder 520)
  - Canadian News Synthesis Project, 1972-1973 (Box 28, Folder 521)
  - Christian Movement for Peace, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 522)
  - Christians for Socialism, 1975-1977, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 523)
  - Frontier Internship in Mission: Reports, 1978-1981 (Box 28, Folder 524)
  - Frontier Internship in Mission: Staff - Francys Valverde, 1979-1980 (Box 28, Folder 525)
  - Frontier Internship in Mission: North American Committee, 1980 (Box 28, Folder 526)
  - Frontier Internship in Mission: Correspondence of Anivaldo Padilha, 1982-1983 (Box 28, Folder 527)
  - Frontier Internship in Mission: General Correspondence, 1984-1986 (Box 28, Folder 528)
  - Frontier Internship in Mission: Candidate Applications, 1985 (Box 28, Folder 529)
  - Frontier Internship in Mission: International Coordinating Committee, 1983-1987 (Box 28, Folder 530-532)
  - Frontier Internship in Mission: I.C.C. Itineration and U.S. Exposure, 1985 Nov 8-10 (Box 28, Folder 533)
  - Frontier Internship in Mission: 25th Anniversary Celebration - New York City, 1985 Nov 6-18 (Box 28, Folder 534-537)
  - Frontier Internship in Mission: Staff - Helene Lackenbauer, 1986-1987 (Box 28, Folder 538)
  - Frontier Internship in Mission: Correspondence re. Sostenes Arruda Macedo, 1986-1987 (Box 29, Folder 539)
  - Frontier Internship in Mission: Meeting re. placement for Sostenes Arruda Macedo - Newark, New Jersey, 1987 Apr (Box 29, Folder 540)
  - Frontier Internship in Mission: Brochures, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 541)
  - Frontier Internship in Mission: Chapter for book by John O'Brien, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 542)
  - Interval House (United Way residential centre for women and children in crisis - Canada) (Box 29, Folder 543)
  - Literacy Working Group, 1977 Oct (Box 29, Folder 544)
  - Lutheran Student Movement in Canada: Publications: One: The Newsletter of the LSM-C, 1979-1980 (Box 29, Folder 545)
  - Lutheran Student Movement in Canada: Publications: YODH: LMSC bi-annual journal, 1978-1979 (Box 29, Folder 545)
  - Lutheran Student Movement in Canada: Miscellaneous documents, 1981 (Box 29, Folder 546)
  - Lutheran Student Movement in Canada: Miscellaneous documents, 1982 (Box 29, Folder 547)
  - Lutheran Student Movement in Canada: Miscellaneous documents, 1983 (Box 29, Folder 548)
  - Lutheran Student Movement in Canada: Miscellaneous documents, 1984-1985 (Box 29, Folder 549)
  - Lutheran Student Movement in Canada: Miscellaneous documents, 1985-1986 (Box 29, Folder 550)
  - Lutheran Student Movement in the U.S.A: Miscellaneous documents, 1975-1976 (Box 29, Folder 551)
  - Lutheran Student Movement in the U.S.A: Miscellaneous documents, 1977 (Box 29, Folder 552)
  - Lutheran Student Movement in the U.S.A: Miscellaneous documents, 1981 (Box 29, Folder 553)
  - Lutheran Student Movement in the U.S.A: Miscellaneous documents, 1982 (Box 29, Folder 554)
  - Lutheran Student Movement in the U.S.A: Miscellaneous documents, 1983 (Box 29, Folder 555)
  - Lutheran Student Movement in the U.S.A: Miscellaneous documents, 1985-1986 (Box 29, Folder 556)
  - Lutheran Student Movement in the U.S.A: Constitution and Statement of Affiliation, 1986-1988 (Box 29, Folder 557)
  - Lutheran Student Movement in the U.S.A: Miscellaneous documents, 1988 (Box 29, Folder 558)
  - National Council of the Churches of Christ-U.S.A. - Division of Overseas Ministries Unit Committee Meeting, 1984 Sep 11-13 (Box 29, Folder 559)
  - National Council of the Churches of Christ-U.S.A. - International Affairs Inter-Unit Working Group, 1978 (Box 29, Folder 560)
  - National Council of the Churches of Christ-U.S.A. (Newspaper), n.d. (Box 29, Folder 561)
  - Newman Conference, 1979 Aug (Box 29, Folder 562)
  - Protestant Foundation at Columbia University, 1976-1977 (Box 29, Folder 563)
  - United Church of Canada - Division of Mission, 1977 Apr (Box 29, Folder 564)
  - United Methodist Church - Board of Global Ministries: "New World Outlook" (journal), 1978 Jul-Aug (Box 29, Folder 565)
  - United Methodist Church - Board of Global Ministries: Mission Intern Program, 1980-1983, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 566)
  - United Methodist Church - Board of Global Ministries: Youth Service Fund, 1973 (Box 29, Folder 567)
  - United Ministries in Education: UME Connexion, 1982, 1986-1987 (Box 30, Folder 568)
  - United Ministries in Education: Convocation - Ft. Worth, Texas, 1984 Jun-Jul (Box 30, Folder 569)
  - United Ministries in Education: Ecumenical Relations Team: Meeting, 1985 Jan 14-15 (Box 30, Folder 570)
  - United Ministries in Education: Ecumenical Relations Team Meeting, 1985 May 8 (Box 30, Folder 571)
  - United Ministries in Education: Ecumenical Relations Team Meeting, 1985 Aug 28 (Box 30, Folder 572)
  - United Ministries in Education: Ecumenical Relations Team Bill Ng's report on Asia trip, 1985 Oct (Box 30, Folder 573)
  - United Ministries in Education: Mailing lists, 1985-1986 (Box 30, Folder 574)
  - United Ministries in Education: New England Region Forum, 1986 Dec 3 (Box 30, Folder 575)
  - United Ministries in Education: Articles, booklets, study materials, 1986, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 576)
  - World Council of Churches - Youth Office - Education and Renewal Unit, 1979, 1983-1984 (Box 30, Folder 577)
  - Young Christians for Global Justice: Miscellaneous documents, 1975, 1977-1978 (Box 30, Folder 578)
  - Young Christians for Global Justice: Miscellaneous documents, 1979 (Box 30, Folder 579)
  - Young Christians for Global Justice: Miscellaneous documents, 1980 (Box 30, Folder 580)
  - Young Christians for Global Justice: Miscellaneous documents, 1981 (Box 30, Folder 581-583)
  - Young Christians for Global Justice: Miscellaneous documents, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 584)
  - Young Christians for Global Justice: Miscellaneous documents, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 585)
  - Young Christians for Global Justice: Miscellaneous documents, 1985 (Box 31, Folder 586)
  - Young Christians for Global Justice: Miscellaneous documents, 1986 (Box 31, Folder 587)
  - Young Christians for Global Justice: 8th Annual Event - "Poverty in North America" - Atlanta, Georgia, 1987 Jan 28-Feb 1 (Box 31, Folder 588)
  - Young Christians for Global Justice: Crosswise Newsletter, 1987-1988 (Box 31, Folder 589)
  - Religious groups organizations in Canada, n.d. (Box 31, Folder 590-592)
- Addendum, Series VI
  - Minutes of the meeting of the Regional Executive, 1980 Feb 8-10 (Box 32, Folder 593)
  - Constitution of the WSCF, 1981 (Box 32, Folder 594)
  - Search Committee for staff, 1980-1981 (Box 32, Folder 595)
  - Correspondence, 1981-1983 (Box 32, Folder 596-597)
  - Minutes, grants, staffing, 1984 (Box 32, Folder 598)
  - Financial records, 1984 (Box 32, Folder 599)
  - Re. John O'Brien, 1984 (Box 32, Folder 600)
  - Address list of supporters, 1985 (Box 32, Folder 601)
  - Financial records, 1985 (Box 32, Folder 602)
  - Financial records, Frontier Internship in Mission program, 1985 (Box 32, Folder 603)
  - Correspondence, 1985 (Box 32, Folder 604)
  - Inter-regional Women's Commission, 1985-1986 (Box 32, Folder 605-606)
  - Trustees meeting minutes, reports, memos, 1985 (Box 32, Folder 607)
  - Trustees meeting minutes, reports, memo, 1986-1988 (Box 32, Folder 608)
  - Financial records, 1986 (Box 32, Folder 609-610)
  - Tax Correspondence, 1986-1988 (Box 33, Folder 611)
  - Universal Day of Prayer for Students liturgies, 1986 (Box 33, Folder 612)
  - NESCC/Campus Ministry correspondence, minutes, 1986-1987 (Box 33, Folder 613)
  - United Methodist correspondence/papers, 1987 (Box 33, Folder 614)
  - Financial records, 1987 (Box 33, Folder 615)
  - Minutes of Trustees, Interim Staffing Committee,WSCF-North American Partners Consultation, memos, reports, 1987 (Box 33, Folder 616)
  - Inter-regional office communications, 1986-1987 (Box 33, Folder 617)
  - Correspondence, 1987 (Box 33, Folder 618)
  - Notes, 1987-1988 (Box 33, Folder 619)
  - Financial records, 1988 (Box 33, Folder 620)
  - Peace with Justice Week, 1988 (Box 33, Folder 621)
  - Correspondence, 1988 (Box 33, Folder 622)
  - Address list, letters re. publications and subscriptions, 1988 (Box 33, Folder 623-624)
  - Travel reports, 1988-1990 (Box 33, Folder 625)
  - Inter-regional office correspondence, 1988 (Box 33, Folder 626)
  - WSCF Executive Committee meeting, Harare, Zimbabwe; WSCF Leadership Conference, Geneva, 1988 (Box 33, Folder 627)
  - Re. staffing, 1989 (Box 33, Folder 628)
  - Notes of John O'Brien, 1988 (Box 33, Folder 629)
  - Perspectives on the Christian Presence in U.S. Universities/College 1960-1994: Working Papers, WSCF Centennial History Project, USA, 1995 (Box 33, Folder 630)
  - Annual report, WSCF North American Region, 2009 (Box 33, Folder 631)
  - Overcoming Violence: Encountering the Past, Engaging the Present, Empowering the Future - Morehouse College, Atlanta (relaunch of Student Christian Movement, USA), 2010 Oct (Box 33, Folder 631)